Hello!!!
Today I will be making some of my home made treats.
I make my home made sweets.
I will make sweets that I made in my house.
Yes, we are starting live delivery!
Yes!
It's started!
Today, a little early.
Yes, sir.
We'll send it to you.
Okay.
I guess everyone's on their way home from work.
Yes, of course.
Good night.
I don't like the term "tired flesh and blood.
"Tired and raw.
Tired, raw
I'm tired, I'm tired
I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired
Good job everyone, thanks for coming in today.
Now let's start the live broadcast of the museum devils!
Live?
Yes, that's right.
How is it that when you have a chunk of text like this, you get it wrong at the most crucial part?
I was afraid I'd make a mistake at the end.
I made a mistake. But it's very reproducible.
Reproducible?
So you always get it right.
Yes, sir.
Is that right? Yes, yes... you get it wrong.
Yes, that's right. It's a compliment.
That's a compliment.
So, everyone, I know it's a little early today.
We will proceed with the recording as soon as possible.
We're going to start recording, so please take a quick look around, and then we'll get started.
We're going to start recording a little bit early today, so please take a look around.
We're getting a lot of "balicata" calls.
Thank you so much!
New
Sparkle, sparkle, sparkle
There's nothing more to it.
It's not like we're in kindergarten or anything.
It's okay.
On the contrary.
So...
I'd like to proceed with the recording.
Have you ever set off fireworks?
I've set off fireworks... which means you're asking me if I've ever set off fireworks.
Why is that so cool?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm not a pyrotechnician, so I can't set off those big ones on my own.
You're right.
You have to be qualified.
Big firecrackers like that...
It's an explosive device, isn't it?
Yes, they are.
You do?
When I was young, I was called "Fireworks Chan.
I was known as the "Fireworks Chan" when I was young... and I loved fireworks.
I'm sure you did it comparatively well.
I've done that relatively often.
You know, the one I have.
I'm sure he'll do it to his buttocks or something.
Everyone does it, don't they?
No, they don't.
It's like a rocket ship.
You mean like that?
Not for me.
It's hot for me.
I don't care how hot it is.
That or something more.
You're supposed to be the one who's going to get out of here with the waist like this.
I wonder if it'll show... stop, stop, stop!
I didn't have a cell phone camera at the time, so did you think it would show?
By the way, Bariho has never shot off fireworks.
I've never seen such a high line perfume
Especially towards the end of summer, there are a lot of firework festivals
There are a lot of fireworks festivals in various places, and there are a lot of fireworks trucks coming around.
I'm sure it's partly due to the performance of the cameras these days.
I think people are getting used to the Aino.
So it's surprisingly difficult to get a good shot of the fireworks with a high quality camera.
It's surprisingly difficult, isn't it?
Especially when the camera is panning like this.
But when you zoom in, you see how blurry the image is, or the timing of when they disappear...
Yes, it's a little bit.
So, first of all, I'd like to introduce you to Marisuzu Tanaka.
I'm sure you'll be able to find a way to get a good shot of the fireworks at Toda Park in Saitama Prefecture, right next to Garaca.
Master!
So...
As you probably know, fireworks these days are all about the big ones.
But it's just a burn... and of course it's nice to see a big flower blooming.
But there are also a lot of little character fireworks.
This is Pikachu.
His face is growing.
Pikachu's face is growing.
Yes, it's true...
How about this heart?
Yes, yes, yes...
I wonder how he does it?
What is it?
We see it as a flat object.
We see it from this side.
But there are people looking at it from different angles.
That's right.
From different angles.
It looks like a heart or a pikachu.
I wonder how the actual fireworks look like.
When you see them in 3D...
That's right.
The gunpowder is poured in one by one, row by row.
They put it in one by one, line by line.
And then they give them colored powder.
His accent is a little funny.
Is that funny?
He said "colored.
No, no.
What's going on?
Did you just come here and change your character?
No, no, no, no.
Let's just keep changing things up.
Yes, of course.
It's fine.
Well, maybe it's just a series of things that make it a circle.
It's just the way it's supposed to be, no matter which way you look at it.
Do you understand? What does it mean?
I have no idea.
Stacks? Is that what you're saying?
It's a series of things.
It's not a pile, is it?
What do you mean, "a pile"?
The powder?
It's a round powder, isn't it?
Yeah, it's like a big ball of gunpowder with a little round powder in it, and it goes boom, boom, boom.
Is he a strange character?
No, no, no, no.
But sometimes they're pointing up.
For example, fireworks in Dreamland sometimes have a mouse like this.
So maybe...
It spins well... What did you say?
What did you say?
Well, I think it's time for you to be quiet.
Let's stop for a second.
You know, like, uh...
I don't know how to say this...
You know these guys.
I think this kind of guy...
There's a ball like this.
Toward various places.
I think it's probably like this...
So no matter where you look
I can see that it looks like this.
But the problem is, it's a character object.
Hmmm...
How do you make Pikachu look like Pikachu from any angle?
I can't keep up with that head of his.
Right?
You're right.
What do you want me to do?
I don't know.
Hey, let's have a pyrotechnician as a guest.
Let's have a pyrotechnician as a guest.
I mean, he's probably busy right now.
It's a little bit off-season.
How did they make that character like that?
It's a complete mystery, isn't it?
Hi, I'm from Hanabi City. I was wondering if anyone here is from Hanabi City.
I'm sure they're very busy right now.
Fireworks are flat. Flat? So maybe...
So maybe they're flat? So if you look at them from a different angle, you won't be able to see them? Yes, I think so.
I see. It's limited.
So this side is either a vertical character or a horizontal character against the circle.
But if it's flat, it makes sense. That's what I was talking about.
I was just talking about that. Yes, we were talking about it. It doesn't matter. It's flat.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
The characters?
Can I ask you to stand up one more time?
Can I ask you to go back one more time?
Can I ask him to retrain in the Force?
May I?
Oh, shit.
If you're doing that, what the hell is this weird traditional art form doing?
This hose is one of those super powers from Star Wars.
Yes, that's right.
It's a terrifying skill that can do things like this to people on its own.
It can even separate lives!
Yes, yes, yes...
Depending on how you use it.
That's right.
Well, well, well...
So, one more thing.
Oh...
There was a fireworks display in Yokohama the other day.
It was right in the Minato Mirai area, so it was very close.
Everyone was on their computers at work.
They're all on their computers at work, talking about how the stock market has crashed.
Are you watching the stock market?
It has to do with the stock market crash and the economy.
And... all sorts of things.
Crying.
Didn't you do that?
It's just you, isn't it?
He's so concerned about it.
I was working on the computer, and all of a sudden...
Suddenly...
Boom! Like that.
It's so close.
And then, you know, they informed me. Well, of course they informed you.
Notice?
You don't let us in on the news, do you?
What news?
Yes, the news.
News?
We didn't have any news.
First of all, I was surprised. And then, I don't know, when I was indoors...
It didn't sound like fireworks at all. It sounded like an explosion.
That's right.
"Pow!
What's that?
It's fireworks, isn't it?
Like, "Isn't that a firework?
They're pretty wayward, aren't they?
Our company is full of thugs.
"Aren't they all fireworks?
Can you see through that? If it's too much trouble...
It's an annual event.
That's what happens.
So...
Mr. Ebe to Yokohama City Minami Ward.
Thank you very much.
And to our regular customers at Obermaster, Mr. Sawapon... and his part-time workers at Ebitu...
The other day there was a fireworks display in my hometown Yokohama!
There are too many people in Minato Mirai area.
So I went to a little distance and tried to shoot fireworks from there!
So the collaboration of the night view of Yokohama and the fireworks was great, right?
Yes, it was!
Isn't this a great place for fireworks?
Isn't this amazing?
What's with all these bright colors?
Amazing!
Wow.
It's amazing!
Green, blue, red, purple...
It's going up this way, too.
This is the Ferris wheel.
It's tiny. Isn't it far away from the night view?
A Ferris wheel. Of course it's a Ferris wheel.
Right?
Yeah, it is, isn't it?
Blah, blah, blah.
Cute blur.
It's a blur.
MJ is here!
I've got MJ! But still... this one is amazing, too.
But this one's amazing, too.
Some pyrotechnicians put their heart and soul into it, and of course they launch them, but they're really elaborate.
I heard it's amazing, with letters coming out and stuff.
I haven't seen them live at all, and I wonder how long it's been since I've seen them.
I haven't seen it live at all during the Corona period, right?
I haven't seen it live for at least 10 years.
If I went now, I'd probably get so excited I wouldn't know what to do.
If the fireworks weren't so loud, I'd probably go with you like this...
I'm scared I'll be like, "Oh, I'm eating, I'm eating.
So the fireworks are beautiful, but the night view of Yokohama is amazing.
It's really beautiful. I'm a Yokohama resident myself, but...
I'm a Yokohama resident, but this is really... amazing from a distance.
I recommend you to go to the future area of the harbor, especially to see the US Bridge.
When you cross the U.S. Bridge, you can see the view from the U.S. Bridge on the lower right.
It's so beautiful, you can see Yokohama like this.
It's a jewel box!
You'll be all Hikomaru.
Yokohama has an amazing night view.
But you know, when there's a fireworks show like this, couples come together, of course.
But before they get together...
Groups of two or three...
They still know who likes whom.
But I don't know what's going to happen.
Here we go!
Just when I confessed my feelings, the fireworks started.
What? Like, "What?
You have one of those? You've never seen anything like that?
You've never seen it? I've never seen or experienced anything like it.
It's just an image.
But it's a great opportunity.
And this one, too... at a shrine or something.
At festivals, there are three or four men and women who come together.
Oh!
What's up with that?
There's a lot of excitement.
Off the beaten path, in the back of the shrine.
Telling and being told.
That's what it's all about.
We all tell and get told.
What's wrong? What happened?
I just thought it'd be nice.
I like her.
Don't all Balikata's friends tell people they like each other?
I wonder if they do.
In their hometown?
There are many festivals in Fukuoka.
In summer, there's Hojo Festival and Dontaku Festival.
They pull us all the way, don't they?
Yeah...
Yeah, it's the last see, because they're desperate.
I still get excited when there's a festival or something.
I like it.
I love it. - I love it.
There were so many couples.
When I was in Yokohama...
Couples...
like the unfinished group from a while ago.
group
about 3 people, 3 men and 3 women.
Ohhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
This is not popular, what are you going to do after this, this is different, this is different from the image, the image is different, if that's the case
I'm going to get drunk... yes, yes, yes, that's why... let's do this too!
Let's go to this one, too.
I got this from Gazelle, from Aho City, Hyogo Prefecture.
Thank you very much!
I'm a member of the Ebi Chu family!
Using freshly made dumpling buns!
I'm sorry.
We have some balicata, too.
But for some reason, the guy who reads it doesn't seem to be a fan of "balikata".
No, it's not.
It's fine.
I write in gyoza dumplings, but I think my heart is balicata.
But I think my heart is in balicata.
Thank you very much.
In my heart.
May I go now?
Yes.
This is... that scientific name.
The hard one.
What's the official name?
Scientific name?
Like the ones you submit for your thesis.
The creature itself is very familiar to us.
They have great names.
Gallus gallus gallus domesticus.
Gallus gallus gallus domesticus
It looks strong. Domestix
Isn't that kinda cool name?
Thank you.
Gallus Gallus Domestix
Gallus Gallus.
Thank you very much.
Gallus Gallus
Gallus Gallus I have to say it with a little bit of momentum to get it out.
I used to have to say "Carry pamu pamu" with a lot of energy, otherwise I couldn't hold my breath.
If I don't say "Carry pamie pamie pamie" twice, it stalls at the end.
Carry pamu pamu pamu.
Gutz, gutz, gutz, gutz, gutz, gutz, gutz.
Big, big, big, big...
It's too loud!
It's so loud.
That feels good.
It's not often that a show shouts out the name of a science so loudly, is it?
No, there aren't.
No, there aren't. Yes, there are.
Living creatures are very familiar to us.
I'm sure you've seen them before.
But if you're asking if they're around here...
I'm not sure.
They don't live in a big city like this.
No, they don't.
I don't think so.
I'm sure they'll be around if we just go a little bit further.
They seem to interact with humans, don't they?
I don't mean to say, "Hey, how are you?" but we shake hands, and we shake hands, and we shake hands, and we say, "How are you?
Domestics... I'm indebted to you every day...
What? Please say that quickly! It's already late!
I've already written it down. Let's start...
Gallus Gallus Domestics!
Why are you doing this?
What's this?
It's not the 3-tiered rose... it's a piggy...
No, not a piggy. It's not a piggy.
Armadillo!
No, Armadillo. What? What do you mean? What? Armadillos, right?
You've never seen an armadillo, have you?
It's more like a dinosaur.
What? Not a dinosaur?
No, no, no, no... if you call it scary, it's a dinosaur.
I don't know...
Please don't lump them all together.
I thought it was a piggy. No, it's not.
But the nose looks like a pig.
What? Isn't an armadillo like this?
But if you look closely... - That's true...
I want to see an armadillo.
Not at all... but... but... look... they look a bit alike.
Well, well, well...
I can imagine the creature.
Then you're right!
You did it!
You didn't do it!
It's supposed to be a shell.
That's right. This is the shell.
That makes a little more sense.
I thought it was meat.
No, no, no, no...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Gus Gallus Gallus.
Wait a minute.
I don't know where to start.
I don't know where to start. Can I calm down for a second?
Take a deep breath.
First of all, what is this?
Four legs, four feet, and a tail, right?
Tails?
I thought it had five tails.
I'm getting used to this Varikat design.
You're right.
I think it's a tail.
It's standing on all four legs.
And this round thing on top of it is probably a face.
Yes, that's right.
A little nose.
Why is there a flag?
I don't know why.
I don't know why the flag is there.
Also...
The flower is emphasized.
It's not a flower.
Not a flower?
The beak.
What's this?
That's a mouth.
But people think beak and mouth
They're supposed to be the same thing.
I've never seen a creature
I've never seen anything like it.
When you open it...
I mean, the lower and upper beaks.
That's right.
That's too high.
Amazing.
Now, let's take a look at what we've been talking about.
What kind of creature is this?
The maestro himself.
A duck.
A duck? A bird?
A bird.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
On the contrary, wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
Ew.
I've never seen a bird before, have you?
No, you haven't, have you?
You're crazy.
Yes, I have.
A foot.
Hmm.
Before you said it was useful.
I thought it was some kind of goat.
But now that I'm home, I can't fix it.
So let's call it a foot.
I'll call it a duck.
I don't feel a camo at all.
Not one bit.
The hair on her head.
Like a crest?
That's true.
Yes, it's there.
It's not a flag?
It's not a flag.
It's just... it looks stupid.
Stupid.
It was amazing... in more ways than one.
It's wonderful.
By the way, Gallus Gallus Domestics...
Yes...
It's a chicken!
Oh! Oh! Oh! Oh!
It's hard to say how close it is.
The quality of the head is inevitable.
Well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well.
Yes, he's a sucker, so we're close in that respect.
I'm always saying...
I'm always saying, for example, to a kindergartener or a child before kindergarten...
I show it to a kindergartener, or a child before kindergarten, and they say, "What is this?" and I say, "A sucker.
I don't think there are any.
I don't think so.
At least not in Yokohama, I'm pretty sure.
Maybe in Fukuoka, maybe.
Don't underestimate Fukuoka.
It's like a little feature on Fukuoka.
It's not a feature at all.
Oh, no.
Well, well, well...
Why is the scientific name "Gallus gallus domesticus"?
I know what "domestics" means.
What do you mean, "Gallus gallus"?
I don't know what "Gallus" means.
Maybe it's like a crying sound.
Like a cock-a-doodle-doo.
That's how it sounds overseas.
Gattesgattes.
He's not crying.
Well, well, well, well...
You know, creature noises...
They sound different depending on where you're from.
It's different in different countries, isn't it?
"Woof woof" sounds like "ba ba ba ba.
In Japan, everyone says "Woof woof".
When it comes to dogs...
In English, it's "bow wow".
Bow-wow.
That's right, they say "bow wow", right?
Yes.
What's wrong?
Gallus is Latin for "male bird.
Why do you say it twice?
Male bird, male bird.
Like stix.
Why do you say it twice?
I wanted to say it so bad.
Male bird, male bird.
You like male birds, don't you?
So you think domestics are...
Domestics are close to each other.
It's like that small area... where the chickens are...
Iwatori is not a bird that can fly so far away...
So, well... well... well, that's why we'd like you to continue to send us your ideas for the creation of living creatures.
Yes, yes, yes...
So, that's all for now...
Well, how was the live delivery?
Maybe.
Maybe... I think so...
I think it's the best place to start.
Yes, this is the best part.
I'm pretty sure that's not a beak.
Let's see what he says, shall we?
Yes, by all means.
I'll take a look.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Maybe there's a riot going on.
Like a riot.
This is what it looked like when I opened it.
That's what it looks like.
And it's all grown back.
So it's body hair.
Yes, it is.
He's surprised.
They're just surprised.
What kind of surprises are we talking about?
Thank you for watching.
I'm a genius, a genius, a genius, a genius!
I'm a bird with four legs... the greatest Balikata master of all time...
I'm sure you're right... 8 times, please be quiet...
I'm sure it's the best of all time...
The truth will become clear.
We still don't know the real culprit.
We still don't know who really did it.
Someone will turn up.
It's big, isn't it?
It's big.
Maybe someday in the future...
Someone in the future will be able to explain this painting.
I don't think it's possible for us to do that now.
It's true, it's a little early.
Maybe 300 years too early.
I agree.
Balikata, I'm here to ask for the Destar car.
Suddenly?
Yeah.
Oh, I miss it.
Digital car
Rally up!
Boom! The one that goes.
Not like this.
It's called a digital car.
It's true.
The first time I did that...
I felt like I was the only one...
Aah! He said, "Oh!
He was moving so much.
So, of course, those of you who watch Barigata on a regular basis have probably noticed this.
He's moving in a strange way, isn't he?
He's a little different from normal human beings.
It's the same with Desasha.
But I really like the way she's standing.
The way she stands...
Standing on the ground like this...
Like this.
He's got his feet firmly on the ground.
Take a big stride.
Don't lose your balance.
It's funny that you stand like this.
Do you stand on your feet so much?
Yes.
Well, you're living life to the fullest, aren't you?
Well, well, well...
Well, that's that, then.
I'll give you the balicata example at the end.
Probably for the delivery.
Yes, that's right.
I'd like you to do it.
That way, everyone will understand.
Then, please do it.
It's "balicata".
Yes, sir.
Bon appétit.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for the other debutantes' charges.
I don't know.
It's on. It's on.
I'm sorry.